export const Users = [
    {
        "id" : 1,
        "quote" : "There was high uncertainty of not getting selected...",
        "name" : "Abhishek Kabi",
        "url" : "abhishek-kabi-png",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "P&G (Supply Chain)",
        "mentalProblem" : "There was high uncertainty of not getting selected by any company, and I was stressed because it was difficult for me to do coding, as it was uninteresting.",
        "mentalSolution": "I started telling myself that CDC is not the end of the journey, and there can be many other ways to get internship.",
        "careerProblem" : "My biggest query was whether I need to put efforts on learning to code or focus on non-tech roles.",
        "careerSolution" : "I realised that while learning to code was a safe and competitive option, but I was definitely not interested in doing it.",
        "roadmap" : "I focused on building my profile around Consult and Supply Chain, learnt about the companies and then individually checked their selection process",
        "resources" : "I relied upon the case study videos on youtube and interview videos of seniors.",
        "message" : "I would suggest you to trust yourself. CDC is not the end, and you have a long way to go.",
        "tags" : "consulting fmcg core strategy on-campus campus 180DC 180 degree dc supply chain industrial"
    },

    {
        "id" : 2,
        "quote" : "I changed my profile a month before CDC...",
        "name" : "Binay Bhattacharya",
        "url" : "binay-bhattacharya-venwiz",
        "mode" : "Off-campus",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Venwiz (Strategy)",
        "mentalProblem" : "I was trapped in the FOMO of CDC and sometimes got into panic attacks. Things seemed to be uncertain during the summer vacation. Seeing my friends working hard behind it, I became more nervous. Even after my internship was sorted off-campus, I used to feel uneasy seeing students cracking big companies.",
        "mentalSolution": "I used to spend time alone in the roof of my hall, and listened to music. That was accompanied with self-talk and affirmations that things will be okay soon, and I will become stronger." ,
        "careerProblem" : "During my summers, I was in a dilemma of which career path to choose. I had learnt web development for internships, and gave coding contests which fetched me good ranks. But as the CDC season arrived, I started losing confidence and my rank started decreasing. I had then started considering strategy and consulting roles.",
        "careerSolution" : "I took some time to think about a career change, but once I was determined, I did not look back. I did a few internships in strategy role and started building my new profile. I changed my path from CDC to off-campus, and ultimately sorted out my upcoming summers in a great company with a good package.",
        "roadmap" : "I tested my coding skills for sometime until I realized that strategy and consulting is a better role for me. I learnt the basics of the career path and started doing off-campus internships. I ultimately got my summer internship offer for a strategy role.",
        "resources" : "Consulting course of Guwahati, Youtube lectures and case analysis of Victor Cheng and mock interview videos were some important resources I followed.",
        "message" : "You have the potential to do anything, but not everything. Figure out what you are actually made for, and once you have made the decision, don't look back again. Every path, wide or narrow, if followed whole-heartedly, will lead you to something miraculous.",
        "tags" : "consulting non-core chemical engineering strategy entrepreneurship startup music singing"
    },
    
    {
        "id" : 3,
        "quote" : "I worked hard for days and nights, but did not get shortlisted...",
        "name" : "Ujjwal Raj",
        "url" : "ujjwal-raj-simpl",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Simpl (SDE)",
        "mentalProblem" : "In summers I worked very hard to learn to code and CP and all. I spent days and nights, and solved hundred of problems. Despite all those, I couldn't see my name shortlisted in any company for days. I started believing that I am not fit for the profile or competition in KGP. Self Doubt on my capabilities started growing inside me. People with malpractices got selected- I used to feel very sad when non-deserving candidates doing malpractice got selected.",
        "mentalSolution": "I kept on solving problems and tried to keep myself occupied all the time. I kept convincing myself that even if I don't get selected I will do a project during my summers. I persuaded myself to keep on coding so that after 1 year (in placements) I will be an awesome coder. I always used to keep myself occupied and motivated that placement is there to help me out anyways. I kept myself busy doing others things like learning new skills, applying off-campus to all job posts in all firms and LinkedIn.",
        "careerProblem" : "I didn't know that there is so much competition in KGP. To be honest, everyone is coding in KGP and this increases the competition. Months before CDC, I didn't do anything else other than CP. I also rejected some internship offers and other activities so that I could prepare well for CDC during my semester and summers as well. But this was not at all necessary. Extra activities and intern would have helped me build my resume better. I would have rather mastered the art of time management than running away from them.",
        "careerSolution" : "I applied in a lot of off-campus job portals, linkedin, and what not. I recreated my cv, gave contests to increase my ratings, and added interesting project in my resume. The best thing I did was that I kept on solving problems everyday. My friends who got the offers used to motivate me to keep doing CP and that helped me a lot keeping me busy during the go.",
        "roadmap" : "During the semester before CDC, I did moderate CP and participated in tech hackathons(Tech GC if in kgp). Added to that, I did a good self project and searched for summer internship under any prof or in a startup. \n During summers, I did hardcore coding (5-6 hrs daily) If you are doing an internship during this phase, learn to manage your time properly.\n During the CDC internship drive, I solved the PYQs of companies, SDE sheet and did revision.",
        "resources" : "The main resources I used were Algozenith, InterviewBit for company-wise PYQs, and GeeksForGeeks (GFG) for regular practice during the drive.",
        "message" : "Keep going. Aim high but always be prepared for any circumstance. CDC is not everything. Placement is there for you anyways.",
        "tags" : "sde software mechanical coding cp dsa competitive programming"
    },
    
    {
        "id" : 4,
        "quote" : "It was haunting to get rejected after interviews on Day-1...",
        "name" : "Shah Dhruv Rajendrabhai",
        "url" : "dhruv-shah-jaguar",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Jaguar (SDE)",
        "mentalProblem" : "One of the most haunting things I experienced in my life was Day 1 of CDC where I was rejected by two companies in which I was shortlisted in Day 1. I was not able to crack the interviews. I was good in the first interview but the question they gave was to be solved in a more efficient way than I did. Due to it I was rejected. The  next went bad because my confidence was dead due to the first. But this shouldn't happen.",
        "mentalSolution": "I talked to my parents as they are my support system. They cheered me up and motivated me for Day 2. I shared with them the whole interview thing, and they just said 'Be confident with your body language and emotions', and their advice worked. I cracked JLR on Day 2. Also I'm a Bhakt of God so I listened some Bhakti songs and read Sunderkaand once. You should be motivated even after the rejections.",
        "careerProblem" : "In my preparation, there were no problems. However, on my first interview od Day 1, a question was to be solved in th best of O(1) time complexity, while I solved in O(log n) and got rejected.",
        "careerSolution" : " Try to give the best answer in interview and get some hints from the interviewer. Along with that, revise your concepts before the interview, and look confident during the interview.",
        "roadmap" : "I just kept doing CP with proper concentration. You shouldn't focus on many things and end up losing everything but should focus on one particular thing at a time.",
        "resources" : "For CP, I did Algozenith and gave contests on CodeForces.",
        "message" : "Trust on yourself and God, and share your problems with your parents (or someone who you trust) as they have seen life more than you and their solutions might work well. Everyone faces tough times, but the one who stays motivated wins the game. ",
        "tags" : "sde software cse computer science coding cp dsa competitive programming"
    },

    {
        "id" : 5,
        "quote" : "I did not have a clear idea of what I wanted to pursue...",
        "name" : "Suman Das",
        "url" : "suman-das-itc",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "ITC (Supply Chain)",
        "mentalProblem" : "It was really mentally draining, specially while applying and checking the CDC mails all the time. And also during the selection process these was a lot of uncertainty regarding whether I made it to the next round. Mentally it was tiring and depressing sometimes.",
        "mentalSolution": "When I got the offer all the anxiety subsided eventually. During the process, talking to seniors and friends helped me gain confidence and guidance on how to go about things. Personally, I kept my expectations as low as possible so that later I wouldn't be disheartened. I realized that I just need to give my best. What happens after that really doesn't matter. It is all cause and effect.",
        "careerProblem" : "Career confusion definitely bugged me a lot. Specifically not knowing the opportunities and lifestyle I would lead after choosing a particular career path. Seniors are always there to help and give guidance, so approaching them would be a very good choice.",
        "careerSolution" : "Talking to my batchmates was the most beneficial thing that I did which helped me get a clear picture of what I really wanted to do and the companies I would like to apply for. I also thought about the life I want to lead and the things I want to do later in life and which career path would better help me pursue those. Finally after I got the offer I was happy that I would get an opportunity to rock in the domain of my choice.",
        "roadmap" : "I was into core Mechanical Engineering and did a few projects which helped me a lot to bag the internship. Also I studied my core subjects well which helped me clear the technical round. The GD round was all about clarity of thought and presence of mind which fortunately i did well in.",
        "resources" : "I read blogs of seniors and talked to them which helped me. Also my class notes were beneficial ",
        "message" : "Just keep calm and go ahead. Something great is waiting for you. Be clear about what you want to do and how you can reach your dreams and goals. ",
        "tags" : "supply chain fmcg core mechanical tfps"
    },

    {
        "id" : 6,
        "quote" : "I recall how hard our parents are working so that we lead a comfortable life...",
        "name" : "Sayan Layek",
        "url" : "sayan-layek-jaguar",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Jaguar (SDE)",
        "mentalProblem" : "When there was a stop in skill growth, I started getting frustrated. This frustration further induced low confidence, and thus, I was then unable to solve easier questions as well.",
        "mentalSolution": "When I get frustrated or depressed, I recall how hard my parents are working to keep me in the race so that I can lead a comfortable life in the future, and I should not let them down.",
        "careerProblem" : "I was not able to improve my coding skills in the summer before Internships. At the same time, I was doing a project under a professor. So, I faced time management issues as well.",
        "careerSolution" : "When I was unable to solve the coding questions of a particular level, I practiced a lot of questions of that level. This is how I improved my coding skills. Talking about the project, I talked to my professor to provide me some time to focus on my CDC journey. So, you often need to clearly speak out your opinion.",
        "roadmap" : "I focused on DSA and coding contests to constantly improve myself. Before the interview, I talked to my mentor and grilled upon my CV and the important keywords used.",
        "resources" : "Codechef and Codeforces for practicing, and hackerrank & Leetcode towards the end helped me a lot.",
        "message" : "There is a beautiful quote by Helen Keller, 'No pessimist ever discovered the secret of the stars, or sailed an uncharted land or opened a new doorway for the human spirit.' So, I believe it is important to stay optimistic in whatever you are doing, because the opposite won't fetch you results anyways. ",
        "tags" : "sde software mechanical engineering coding cp dsa competitive programming"
    },

    {
        "id" : 7,
        "quote" : "I stopped worrying about the WHAT IF's and focused on HOW TO...",
        "name" : "Pushparaj Singh",
        "url" : "pushparaj-singh-amazon",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Amazon (SDE)",
        "mentalProblem" : "I didn't face any significant mental health issues. Talking precisely, I did not get into any significant FOMO or peer pressure.",
        "mentalSolution": "I believe on the thought, 'If it happens, well and good. However, if it does not happen, will see'. And this keeps me stress-free.",
        "careerProblem" : "I faced conceptual problems in DSA, for topics like graphs. It was difficult for me at the first glance to solve these questions.",
        "careerSolution" : "I gave it time, and just kept practising questions. Ultimately i was able to understand the flow of the concept.",
        "roadmap" : "I started preparing around April-May for the internship drive. Your dept CGPA is important when considered SDE. POR and Projects were not that valuable for this role.",
        "resources" : "GFG practice worked the best as a resource for me.",
        "message" : "Luck often plays a significant role in your life events. It may be in favour or against you. Don't take things too seriously. ",
        "tags" : "sde software non-core chemical engineering coding cp dsa competitive programming"
    },

    {
        "id" : 8,
        "quote" : "If you know DSA, then cracking the first few tests will be easier for you...",
        "name" : "Vedant Gulve",
        "url" : "vedant-gulve-calgary",
        "mode" : "MITACS",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "University of Calgary (ML)",
        "mentalProblem" : "I was highly uncertain about which university I would get, and that confusion made me feel low at times.",
        "mentalSolution": "I talked to the closed ones at my home, and they motivated me to stress less, and explore the opportunities available in front of me.",
        "careerProblem" : "Just like anyone else, I was initially confused about what to pursue in my career. I ultimately continued with machine learning.",
        "careerSolution" : "I searched for some good foreign university projects and learnt a lot of skills by working on them. I got a confidence boost when I was finally selected.",
        "roadmap" : "I began with ML and data and started building my skills. Then I got a project off-campus that helped me brush up my skills and explore new dimensions of machine learning. Finally I got an offer through MITACS.",
        "resources" : "Coursera ML courses and Andrew NG courses on youtube proved to be a great resource for me.",
        "message" : "If you are willing to get into technical profile, then I would advise you to learn and practice DSA (data structure and algorithm), so that it is not difficult for you to crack the coding tests.",
        "tags" : "ml machine learning data science analytics electronics electrical engineering non-core"
    },

    {
        "id" : 9,
        "quote" : "I started my preparation for internships quite late...",
        "name" : "Suhas AM",
        "url" : "suhas-am-jio",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Jio (SDE)",
        "mentalProblem" : "I had started my preparation for the CDC internships so late, and was worried about what would happen now. Everyone else around me was much more prepared.",
        "mentalSolution": "What helped me to come out of my low self-esteem  was to practically face the coding tests and interviews.",
        "careerProblem" : "I was lacking in my preparation and that also reflected in my interviews. It was difficult for me to solve the coding questions that could have been easily solved given that I had a better preparation by starting earlier.",
        "careerSolution" : "I faced the tests and interviews and observed the kind of questions being ask3ed. Accordingly, I continued with my preparation, leaving no stones unturned in the remaining time.",
        "roadmap" : "I started my internship preparation in the last half of the month of July. I did not appear for any competitive coding contests. I practised a lot of questions of the main topics of DSA.",
        "resources" : "The main resources used by me were Leetcode, Codechef, and youtube videos.",
        "message" : "Keep yourself updated with the process. Contact your seniors to know their experiences.",
        "tags" : "sde software computer science engineering cse coding cp dsa competitive programming"
    },

    {
        "id" : 10,
        "quote" : "Being from non-circuital branch, I was worried about the competition...",
        "name" : "Anushka Chatterjee",
        "url" : "anushka-chatterjee-nomura",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Nomura (Finance)",
        "mentalProblem" : "Belonging to a non-circuital department, I was always worried that maximum of the companies won't open for me or even if they do they won't prefer us over circuital department students. The competition is pretty high in IIT Kharagpur. All these things made me worried about getting an internship during CDC.",
        "mentalSolution": "I talked with my seniors and communicated to them about my issues. All of them were very helpful and comforting and guided me on how I need to prepare myself so that I can get an internship. They shared with me their stories about how their condition was not very different from mine and still they managed yo do well. This motivated me to try harder.",
        "careerProblem" : "My coding skills weren't very good and most of the companies took CP tests for their selection. The competition in IIT Kharagpur is anyways too high. All these things made me worried about getting an internship during CDC.",
        "careerSolution" : "I took the guidance of my seniors to understand the kind of questions they faced during their interviews. I prepared myself accordingly.",
        "roadmap" : "I had already done 2-3 internships (mainly in ML/AI domain) by the end of my 2nd year and had started practising CP (covering it's topics). However, I mainly did my preparation in the summer holidays. First I completed learning all the important CP topics and kept giving tests in the coding platforms to get a time bound practice. Next I brushed my probability and statistics concepts and practised questions on that as well. In the last month I went through puzzles, case studies, ML concepts.",
        "resources" : "For Cp, I used Algozenith, leetcode and InterviewBit. I covered my Probability and Statistics from Stats 110 by Harvard University. Other than that, I revised my older concepts of Machine Learning.",
        "message" : "Be confident during tests and interviews. Do not get frustrated or carried away looking at other people. Everyone has a separate journey. Keep trying till the end.  Many companies come and it is a very long process. Being persistent and not giving up is the key. All the best!",
        "tags" : "chemical engineering finance non-tech non-core"
    },

    {
        "id" : 11,
        "quote" : "I was trying to focus on multiple profiles and lacked focus...",
        "name" : "Aryan Gupta",
        "url" : "aryan-gupta-amazon",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Amazon (SDE)",
        "mentalProblem" : "The main problem that I faced would be the anxiety of performance and peer pressure. You feel a constant need to perform and for obvious reasons, it's hard to find guidance for nuisances when everyone is trying to sort out themselves.",
        "mentalSolution": "My main focus was being self evaluative, understanding the situation and the scenario that I was facing. It was important to acknowledge that certain outcomes, negative or positive, were beyond control and there was no reason to worry about them.",
        "careerProblem" : "I had my focus in technology driven domains. But didn't specifically focus on Software, Data or Machine Learning. This diverted my focus due to the variety I was trying to cover to improve my chances.",
        "careerSolution" : "I didn't take any active decisions in this regard. I wanted to maximize my chances by trying it all out given the luck factor in the process.",
        "roadmap" : "I had a clear mindset that I wished to tread into the software development domain and build core utilities that actually create impact. So I did many projects to learn the workflow involved(My interest in IOT was a bonus). Data Structures and Algorithms were necessary to go ahead.",
        "resources" : "YouTube was the biggest helper.(Documents compiled by seniors are good guidance for resources.)",
        "message" : "Try to keep calm and stay focused and there is a lot of life left ahead so it is only a plus to achieve something at this early a stage. This process is good enough to give you a jolt of action so that you take steps to become industry-ready. Try learning stuff that you think is gonna be a game changer and necessity for the future.",
        "tags" : "sde software chemical engineering coding cp dsa competitive programming"
    },

    {
        "id" : 12,
        "quote" : "I often felt unprepared just before the scheduled interviews...",
        "name" : "Yash Jangade",
        "url" : "yash-jangade-drreddy",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Dr. Reddy (Core)",
        "mentalProblem" : "During CDC, there is always a huge peer pressure as your friends would get internship offers before you, etc. Also, as we were notified about the interviews before 7-8 hours, there was always a sense of unpreparedness which just made me feel tensed and nervous. The CDC process was dynamic and would test your emotional strength.",
        "mentalSolution": "The best solution for this for me was to talk with friends. They had a solution for every problem. Also, before interview if I felt tensed, I practiced some breathing exercise to calm down.",
        "careerProblem" : "It was difficult to decide which career path was best for me. Also, there was no proper roadmap for preparation. ",
        "careerSolution" : "I consulted with many seniors and they helped me find the most suitable career for me as per my skills.",
        "roadmap" : "I was focused on 3 careers: FMCG, core and product profile. I prepared for them simultaneously and got placed in a chemical core company.",
        "resources" : "I followed 'swipe to unlock', 'How to crack PM interviews' and 'decode and conquer' for product profile. For FMCG, I used 'Basic Supply chain Management'. Finally for my core, I used the course material of Chemical Engineering.",
        "message" : "If you are sitting for CDC, don't just prepare the subject matter, prepare yourselves to sustain the huge pressure which you face during the process. Keep in touch with the seniors as they will guide you and talk with friends about your problem, they will help you tackle that problem. Rest you can study for the test and interviews by yourselves. All the Best!!! :)",
        "tags" : "core chemical engineering product fmcg non-technical"
    },

    {
        "id" : 13,
        "quote" : "I believed that if I trained myself, I would achieve what I want...",
        "name" : "Subhajit Chowdhury",
        "url" : "subhajit-chowdhury-project",
        "mode" : "Off-campus",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Project (Core)",
        "mentalProblem" : "There was no exclusive load or stress for me during the time, as I knew that I was not totally prepared for it.",
        "mentalSolution": "I believed that if I train myself properly into any field, i would get a role easily.",
        "careerProblem" : "I was not clear about which role to pursue. I realised that coding is not a good profile for me.",
        "careerSolution" : "I explored different profiles like product, data, etc. through courses and internships.",
        "roadmap" : "I was not too serious about the CDC internships. I used this time to explore different profiles to figure out what suites me the best. Around January, I got a project in core for the coming summers.",
        "resources" : "My main resources were my course material.",
        "message" : "I would just say that it's not fruitful to worry about what the other people are doing around you. You are young right now. Explore the various opportunities in front of you.",
        "tags" : "core chemical engineering off-campus project non-technical"
    },

    {
        "id" : 14,
        "quote" : "There was a phase when I was not getting shortlisted by any company...",
        "name" : "Priyam Goenka",
        "url" : "priyam-goenka-zomato",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Zomato (SDE)",
        "mentalProblem" : "I was constantly worried about the CDC process and doubted if I would get a chance for an internship, seeing the high competition in IIT Kharagpur.",
        "mentalSolution": "I realised that I am not alone in the journey and many people around me are hustling and struggling to get through it. So, this decreased my FOMO.",
        "careerProblem" : "I was doing well with the DSA prep, and was able to solve the coding test questions. However, there was a long phase when I didn't get shortlisted. I had left practicing questions of coding for a while because of the low self-esteem induced due to this.",
        "careerSolution" : "When I got shortlisted for Zomato, i spent the next 2-3 days brushing up my skills so that i could decently solve the interview questions.",
        "roadmap" : "I gave coding contests and practiced DSA questions. The initial few interviews were difficult to crack. I once got shortlisted for a core company, but i stuck to my ideology of continuing in my domain of interest.",
        "resources" : "My main resources were Algozenith and coding contests.",
        "message" : "Prepare well for your CDC, but even if you don't get through it, you will have enormous opportunities off-campus. Stay updated and stay in practice.",
        "tags" : "sde software non-core chemical engineering coding cp dsa competitive programming"
    },

    {
        "id" : 15,
        "quote" : "I got multiple interview opportunities, but could not get selected in any...",
        "name" : "Aritra Mitra",
        "url" : "aritra-mitra-maxplank",
        "mode" : "Off-campus",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Max Plank (ML)",
        "mentalProblem" : "During my MITACS journey, I got multiple interview opportunities, but could not get selected. It got me into a bit of stress sometimes.",
        "mentalSolution": "My approach to the stress was to let that shit go, and focus on what I am doing right now. Something else would definitely come on the way.",
        "careerProblem" : "There was a phase when I was unable to work efficiently and procrastinated about it. That resulted in low marks in test and then that got me motivated for working harder.",
        "careerSolution" : "I talked to some professors of my college associated with the university I was willing to apply for, to understand the requirements and skills needed. That gave me a lot of clarity.",
        "roadmap" : "I did projects towards the end of my second year, and got an LOR (Letter of Recommendation). I further explored my field of interest. I filled the MITACS form because I believed that working in foreign will give me some exposure to varied culture and i will get to learn a lot from that experience.",
        "resources" : "Stack Overflow and YouTube have proven to be great resources for me.",
        "message" : "Have fun, but keep a good CGPA. Attempt everywhere for off campus. Get an LOR from professors at the end of second year. Choose judiciously among multiple options, on the basis of the importance of your organisation in that profile.",
        "tags" : "ml machine learning data science analytics cse computer science and engineering non-core"
    },

    {
        "id" : 16,
        "quote" : "My growth had become stagnant for a while, and nothing seemed to work...",
        "name" : "Lakshay Singh",
        "url" : "lakshay-singh-bnymellon",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "BNY Mellon (SDE)",
        "mentalProblem" : "I saw my friends around me getting selected for internships. And that caused a lot of FOMO and stress in me.",
        "mentalSolution": "I used the stress positively to increase my level of preparation for the interviews and coding tests.",
        "careerProblem" : "There was a time when my growth in coding seemed to become stagnant. I used a lot of ways to get better again but nothing seemed to work for me.",
        "careerSolution" : "I visited home in my summer holidays and chilled with my family for a while. I began my preparation again with a fresh mindset and henceforth continued my growth.",
        "roadmap" : "I started giving coding contests quite early, in my second year. I spent the summers preparing for coding rounds.",
        "resources" : "The main resources that I used for my preparation were GeeksForGeeks (GFG), YouTube and LeetCode.",
        "message" : "It is beneficial to maintain a good CGPA, and it helps in the shortlisting. However, it is not the only factor affecting selections. You will face failures on the path, turn them into success milestones by learning the lessons from your failures.",
        "tags" : "sde software non-core electrical engineering coding cp dsa competitive programming"
    },

    {
        "id" : 17,
        "quote" : "I was very unclear about my career, and that was reflected in interviews...",
        "name" : "Vikram S.",
        "url" : "vikram-s-drreddy",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Dr. Reddy (Core)",
        "mentalProblem" : "I was really dissapointed when I was unable to clear the final round of ITC. That was a time when I felt that I need to get used to failures. I realised that CDC is not just about getting an internship. It is more about building yourself inside out.",
        "mentalSolution": "I realised that I should not keep thinking about it. After sometime my thought process was that if it's made to happen, it will happen. Else, you will have other opportunities.",
        "careerProblem" : "I was preparing for my core but I didn't work much upon my way of presentation during interviews. I was very unclear about my career and that was reflected in my interview rounds.",
        "careerSolution" : "I went through the interview tips and did significant self introspection to get clarity of what I am actually doing and want from my future, so that the HR gets a clear picture of me.",
        "roadmap" : "I had done an internship in data profile, and made resume for data and core. I checked out the priorities in each of these roles and the kind of topics important for them. I got shortlisted for ITC, cleared the GD and tech rounds but didn't clear the final round. Ultimately after honing my skills and learning from failures, I grabbed an opportunity at Dr. Reddy.",
        "resources" : "The main resources that I used for my preparation were my course material, notes and YouTube videos.",
        "message" : "Everyone will ultimately get an internship. You don't have to stress about it. It is more important to develop your personality and find out your interests. Don't copy people, otherwise there won't be any difference between you and others.",
        "tags" : "core chemical engineering data technical non-technical"
    },

    {
        "id" : 18,
        "quote" : "I got multiple interview opportunities, but could not get selected in any...",
        "name" : "Vinod Meena",
        "url" : "vinod-meena-uber",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Uber (SDE)",
        "mentalProblem" : "I began my preparation for the CDC internship role as an SDE starting in May. However, I encountered challenges due to internet issues at my home, so I had to join a library that was quite a distance away from my home. I relied on various coding platforms, particularly Codeforces, to practice competitive programming. Despite the inconvenience of having to travel to the library daily, I diligently prepared there for two months.",
        "mentalSolution": "To cope with the mental challenges during my CDC (Campus Development Cell) preparation, I have implemented several strategies. First, I regularly stayed in touch with my seniors and batchmates who provided me motivation and guidance. They had been there for me during difficult times and helped me with my preparation. Additionally, when I felt low on confidence, I talked to my friends to refresh my mind and uplift my spirit. Taking regular breaks and enjoying a holiday once a week has also been a helpful strategy to rejuvenate myself and prepare for the next six days with renewed energy. Overall, these approaches have been beneficial in managing my mental well-being during my CDC preparation.",
        "careerProblem" : "I already decided that i go for SDE role so that I did not face any severe problem in my career.",
        "careerSolution" : "I did not face any significant career problems.",
        "roadmap" : "During my preparation i mostly focused on CP so I prepared for DSA and i started practicing dsa problems from codeforces and also i gave all contests during that time that things boost up my problem solving skills. After mid june i also start preparing for interview based problems from gfg. I gave some mock interviews also.",
        "resources" : "The main resources I used were YouTube, GeeksForGeeks (GFG), CodeForces, CSES and CodeChef.",
        "message" : "It's important to always believe in yourself and maintain your confidence, regardless of the outcome of a single interview. Success can come from different paths, whether it's acing the first interview or persevering after facing setbacks from previous interviews. Instead of feeling disappointed after one failure, shift your focus towards seeking out the next opportunity to learn and grow. Remember that success is not limited to a singular event, but rather a continuous journey of self-improvement and resilience. Stay positive, keep pushing forward, and embrace the possibilities that lie ahead.",
        "tags" : "sde software cse computer science coding cp dsa competitive programming"
    },

    {
        "id" : 19,
        "quote" : "I felt quite rushed and unprepared before the interview...",
        "name" : "Vivek Jaiswal",
        "url" : "vivek-jaiswal-sprinklr",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Sprinklr (SDE)",
        "mentalProblem" : "The main problem I faced was the hectic schedule on the interview day. I got a call from CDC team about the interview, and the mobile was initially silent. So I took a while to pick the call. I then had to hurriedly get ready for the interview. ",
        "mentalSolution": "I assured myself that it's an experience and even if I don't get the internship, it's just Day-1 and I will get a lot of chances.",
        "careerProblem" : "There was no noticeable career issues that I faced.",
        "careerSolution" : "There was no noticeable career issues that I faced.",
        "roadmap" : "I achieved 5 star rating in CodeChef in just 5 contests. I followed my CSE courses to practice the concepts of DSA. I ultimately cracked my internship on Day-1.",
        "resources" : "The main resources I used were Stack Overflow, youtube videos and CSE study material.",
        "message" : "Don't take your failures too seriously. You will get a lot of chances in your life ahead. Just trust yourself and take it easy. All the best!",
        "tags" : "sde software cse computer science coding cp dsa competitive programming"
    },

    {
        "id" : 20,
        "quote" : "It was frustrating when I was not being shortlisted for the next rounds...",
        "name" : "Janhvi Haldwania",
        "url" : "janhvi-haldwania-vedanta-winniped",
        "mode" : "CDC & MITACS",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Vedanta & University of Winniped (Mining core)",
        "mentalProblem" : "I saw my friends getting selected for the internships. It often created a sense of fomo for me during the process. This anxiety could have affected my consistency and preparation.",
        "mentalSolution": "I had friends who were in the same position as me, and could relate to my situation. I shared my issues with them, and felt better to know that I am not alone. Feeling supported helps you tackle anxiety and regain focus.",
        "careerProblem" : "The CDC process was initially not very clear to me, and I was also not clear about which profile to pursue. I tried to explore multiple profiles to get multiple shortlists, but ultimately trying hands in multiple profiles wouldn't help.",
        "careerSolution" : "After exploring a few profiles like software and product, I made a decision to go ahead with machine learning, and side-by-side continued the preparation for my core (mining).",
        "roadmap" : "Talking about CDC, I would say that the chances of cracking your core company are enhanced by the type of projects you list out, and the way you present yourself in the interview. CDC also has a factor of luck, so I would not recommend you to get disheartened by rejections. Further talking about MITACS, the main crux is creating a good CV, listing relevant projects and getting LOR from professors. The interview process is not much difficult, so make sure to create a good first impression through your CV and application.",
        "resources" : "Coursera and Udemy courses on Machine Learning, youtube videos and the 50 problems set book on Probability and Statistics are some crucial resources that can help you in the data profile. Other than that, I would recommend participating in Kaggle competitions for being better at Data.",
        "message" : "Don't lose hopes. The process may seem to be depressing, but stay consistent and keep putting real efforts. You will ultimately get the results that you deserve.",
        "tags" : "core mining engineering data ml machine learning science"
    },

    {
        "id" : 21,
        "quote" : "Giving multiple tests everyday led to a bad sleep schedule...",
        "name" : "Harshit Patel",
        "url" : "harshit-patel-drreddy",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Dr. Reddy (Core)",
        "mentalProblem" : "During CDC, we need to give a lot of tests everyday, which was very frustrating for me and this also disturbed sleep schedule and led to accumulation of mental stress.",
        "mentalSolution": "To be honest, just keep calm, try to take proper sleep when possible and mentally prepare yourself for this beforehand.",
        "careerProblem" : "There are a lot of problems regarding this, one particular is regarding everyone applying for SDE role even when they don't have any interest in that role careerwise. It also creates fomo for the students pursuing other profiles.",
        "careerSolution" : "I tried to apply only to those companies that I was confident to continue if I got selected.",
        "roadmap" : "I followed the resources previously compiled by seniors as roadmap.",
        "resources" : " ",
        "message" : "Just stay confident, and last but not the least, trust yourself even when you are feeling very low.",
        "tags" : "core chemical engineering non-technical"
    },

    {
        "id" : 22,
        "quote" : "My confidence broke when I was not getting shortlisted for a long time...",
        "name" : "Soumik Subhra Biswas",
        "url" : "soumik-biswas-axisbank",
        "mode" : "CDC",
        "college" : "IIT Kharagpur",
        "company" : "Axis Bank (SDE)",
        "mentalProblem" : "In the beginning, I had felt that I had prepared myself well enough to get my CDC sorted. But gradually I realised that the competition is not as easy as I had perceived it to be. Everyone prepares themselves really well and when I couldn't manage a single shortlist during the initial days of the internships, it really brought my confidence down. But as the saying goes, you just need to grab that one opportunity which life gives you.",
        "mentalSolution": "I was regularly in touch with seniors some of whom had faced the same situation during their CDC internship tests. They provided the best guidance possible and regularly told me not to lose hopes. Only 40-50% of the people sitting for CDC manage to get their internships sorted, but it has nothing to do with whether he will manage to get a good placement. This belief kept me going. My suggestion to the upcoming batch would be to regularly stay in touch with your seniors and batchmates, because they are the ones who are going to keep you motivated. ",
        "careerProblem" : "I had mostly prepared for coding rounds and had only a mere knowledge about basics of Machine Learning but during my CDC tests, I felt like I should have prepared myself for Machine Learning equally as I had stressed on coding. I must accept the fact that due to staying at home during the first 3 semesters, I did not know many seniors whom I can contact for guidance. As a result, I feel like I received the required guidance a bit late. I did not have any good project to write in my CV till the summer vacation before CDC, since I did not have many skills before that.",
        "careerSolution" : "Algozenith played a significant role in providing me with the right guidance. And as I have mentioned previously, seniors were really helpful too. During the CV submission period, I shared my CV with multiple seniors who provided me with valuable insights about the changes that must be made in the CV.",
        "roadmap" : "I had coding experiences in Python, C and C++ from first year itself. I had started preparing myself for coding rounds from December. However, the preparation started in full-swing only during the summer vacation. During the summer vacation, I started solving coding problems on AlgoZenith platform and Leetcode digilently. I also did a bit of competitive programming initially, but stopped it when I got to know that mostly CDC coding round questions are quite different from CP questions. Rather, seniors suggested me to solve questions on Leetcode and AlgoZenith. Although Axis Bank had asked for coding questions in Python, but I believe my experiences in DSA came handy. I had also worked on Guesstimates and probability and statistics questions during my CDC journey which also came in handy. I had also prepared every point of my CV really well. I along with my wing-mates also conducted mock interviews among ourselves to prepare well for the interviews.",
        "resources" : "I practised coding problems from the AlgoZenith coding platform and Leetcode which were quite useful. I also worked on a project involving web development and implementing a search engine algorithm in Python. I had developed these skills simply from various YouTube  During my interview, I was asked to explain this project in detail. I also practised puzzles and probability and statistics questions from GFG.",
        "message" : "Just trust yourself. Stay in touch with your friends and seniors. They will motivate you and guide you to get your BT sorted.",
        "tags" : "non-core chemical engineering technical dsa cp competitive programming algozenith"
    }
]